(Space Rice Cake)
(Just another ordinary commute)
(A guest was already there for a surprise appearance.)
(Doh Kyung Soo, the seasoned part-timer)
(No, that's not right.)
(Like this...)
(Under the strict director's supervision,)
(they sweated buckets learning to make a new dish.)
(Rice cracker taco)
(The perfect director's sweet and caring side...)
(made them smile despite the exhaustion.)
(He was leading the team smoothly.)
(But once he started serving customers,)
(his cool director charisma vanished.)
(The shrimp burger is included, right?)
(He turned into a nervous wreck, just like a rookie part-timer.)
(When will you start making the taco?)
(We'll start as soon as an order comes in.)
(I think I left it off the order.)
Did they order it?
(They're working with the part-timer who keeps making mistakes.)
(Did you seek out hardships?)
- Mi Hyun. - Yes?
This one is way too dark. What should we do?
I only fried it for a minute.
- It was in the fryer for a minute? - Yes, the oil was at 200°C.
No, you shouldn't set the temperature to 200°C.
It shouldn't be at 200°C. Let's fry a new one.
- Let's start over again. - Hold on.
We shouldn't fry it at 200°C, right?
That's right. The temperature is perfect now.
- Young Ji, I put it in the fryer. - Okay.
(Tension fills the kitchen.)
- You can check it later. - Okay.
(Yu Jin is prepping pizza.)
This is a disaster.
It's because it's bigger than the tray.
But with the powder, it doesn't stick here.
(The patty is burnt.)
It's okay. How...
What should we do about this?
Should we cut it?
- Rather than keep that part. - You think so?
(Pure chaos in the kitchen)
(Screaming and chatting)
A new group of customers is here.
(In the middle of the chaos, new customers arrive.)
May I take your name, please?
(She has to take their order too.)
- Yes. - Can we have one shrimp burger...
- Yes. - and one taco, please?
- Of course. - And...
- one cake, please. - Sure.
Can we also have one glass of pomegranate ade...
- and two glasses of yuzu ade? - Okay.
- I'll give you the receipt. - One shrimp burger...
(But...)
I'm sorry, ma'am.
- I'll redo the payment for you. - Okay.
- I'll add one glass of yuzu ade. - Okay.
(She redoes the payment.)
- Yes. - We're ready to order.
All right.
(Drink Order: 1 pomegranate ade, 2 yuzu ades)
(A total of 3 glasses)
My mind was all over the place. This one has been served.
(But, on the ticket...)
(Drink Order: Pomegranate ade included in the combo)
(One more glass of yuzu ade?)
The drinks that are ready...
- Thanks. Should we serve them? - Yes.
- Let's just serve them first. - Okay. I'll be right back.
- Before the ice melts. - Okay.
- Table Seven. I'll be right back. - Yes.
Yes, I'm carrying the drinks.
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Eun Ji, when will our ades be served?
- What dishes did you order? - I meant the ades.
- Right. I'll bring them right over. - One of them is pomegranate ade.
I'm very sorry. These are for that table.
Really?
That's okay. No problem.
That was a close call.
- They're for us, right? - Thank you for pointing that out.
- Thank you so much. - They're for Table Seven.
- Yes... - Because we came first.
Exactly. I totally understand.
- Please help me out for a second. - Okay.
You ordered one shrimp burger, right?
- Yes. - How much is it?
Right here...
(They're huddled up like a study group.)
Could I just cancel everything...
- and redo the payment? - Sure.
- Got it. - That'll be no problem.
- If you give me your credit card... - Did we order tacos too?
Taco? Oh, right.
We ordered one taco as well.
Okay.
You didn't order any tacos...
(Yes, they did.)
- Yes, we did. - Yes.
- Did you order tacos? - Yes.
(The more they analyze the order, the more confused they get.)
All together, your total comes to...
I'll tell you when you go home.
- Okay. I understand. - Okay.
- I'll be back with your food. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Their study group session is over, but they're left with homework.)
Is anything confusing you?
- Yes, this one. - Right.
- I messed up the order. - Are we down one yuzu ade?
But I took care of it.
One carrot... Oh, we got one taco for this order.
- Was it on the ticket? - No, there was no taco on it.
- Let me clear this up. - Okay.
Mi Hyun, I took the order incorrectly earlier.
- Please make one taco. - Sure.
Thank you.
- Kyung Soo. - Yes?
Can you make two glasses of pomegranate ade...
and one glass of yuzu ade for me?
- I'm working on it right now. - Okay.
We have perfect teamwork.
Today, I feel like we've finally hit our stride.
(She's calmly making a shrimp burger.)
One shrimp burger is up.
Okay.
One more taco is ready.
Got it.
The carrot cake and taco.
It's perfect.
(Table 8: 1 shrimp burger combo, 1 taco, 1 carrot cake)
(The part-timer made 3 glasses of ade skillfully.)
These are all for Table Eight.
- I'll serve them to Table Eight. - A shrimp burger, a carrot cake...
(The dishes have been made in an instant.)
Hello.
(The food is served instantly to minimize the wait.)
- Thank you. - Here's your food.
(Table 8: Everything has been served.)
Here's the taco.
- Here's your pizza. - Our food is here.
Oh, great.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
(Every dish has been served!)
(She's pausing for a quick breather.)
(We're waiting for customers)
(Maru sniffs, Maru perks up)
(Maru snatches)
(Maru zooms and zooms)
(Our little puppy is waiting for customers.)
(Walking)
(The long-awaited party of 4 arrives.)
(But then...)
(Another party of 4 walks in.)
(All 8 customers arrive at the same time.)
- I'll serve the food. - Okay.
- Welcome. - Hello.
Hello.
He's fast.
(Oh, my. He's fast.)
He was moving at supersonic speed just now.
- We got a new order. - Yes, sir.
One pizza, one taco,
one carrot cake, and one beef burger.
one shrimp burger, and one beef burger.
- Got it. - Got it.
One pizza.
- One pizza and one taco. - One pizza.
Okay.
(Oiling the pan to get ready for the taco)
(In goes a big ladleful of minced meat.)
(Infusing the meat with the rich aroma of garlic)
(Next, adding the taco seasoning, the key to the whole flavor)
(Stir-frying everything until the flavors are perfectly combined)
(Topped with refreshing tomato salsa...)
(and savory avocados)
I'll take it out, Mi Hyun.
Okay.
(Squeezing on a generous amount of sour cream)
One taco is ready.
(As Mimi wraps up the taco,)
(her partner Young Ji starts prepping the beef burger.)
I want them to eat it while it's warm.
(And she fries a shrimp patty...)
(and tater tots perfectly.)
(Their positions are switched, but their professional mode stays on.)
Okay.
(Meanwhile, Yu Jin plates the pizza.)
Yu Jin, if you're busy, I'll do it.
- I'm fine for now. - Okay.
Yu Jin, I'll serve the cake.
Thank you.
Then I should make the ade, right?
(The service team has great teamwork.)
(The part-timer makes the ade skillfully.)
(Right then, a group of customers leaves.)
(Once the customers leave,)
(the next mission awaits.)
Kyung Soo,
please go upstairs and clear the table.
(While Kyung Soo cheerfully clears the table...)
One taco is ready.
The pizza is ready.
(After they serve food busily...)
Goodness. This is exhausting.
(Empty plates start coming out.)
(The service team takes turns doing the dishes.)
You served the pizza earlier...
We should cross this one off.
We should cross this one off too.
- This one is out. - Is it out?
It's out.
But the drinks aren't ready yet.
(They didn't have time to make the ades.)
If you make two glasses each of pomegranate and yuzu ade,
- I'll serve them on this tray. - Okay.
- Two pomegranate and two yuzu. - You're so smart.
Two yuzu and one pomegranate, Yu Jin?
- Two of each. - Okay.
Thank you, Yu Jin.
- Don't mention it. - Oh, gosh.
(The ade, as refreshing as Yu Jin, is ready.)
I'm going to serve one carrot cake too.
(Following the drinks, the carrot cake is ready too.)
- These are for Table Ten. - Eun Ji, this is for...
(Table 10: 1 mint carrot cake, 2 pomegranate ades, 2 yuzu ades)
One carrot cake.
Thank you so much.
(So she arrived at the destination?)
Please stir it well before you drink it.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(The ades have been served to the wrong table.)
(Actually...)
(We're Table 10.)
- You ordered a carrot cake, right? - Yes.
- Thank you. - Here you go. Thank you.
(Fortunately, she served the cake to the right table.)
(Table 10: 1 mint carrot cake)
(Meanwhile, Yu Jin fills the next tray.)
(Table 11: 1 mint carrot cake, 2 pomegranate ades, 2 yuzu ades)
(It's the exact same menu combination.)
- Kyung Soo, can you go to Table 11? - Sure.
These are all for Table 11.
- Table 11? - Yes, they're all for Table 11.
(Table 11)
(Pausing)
(They already have their ades.)
(The part-timer is holding a tray fully loaded with ades.)
(Stepping backward)
- These aren't for Table 11. - What's going on?
- They're not for Table 11? - They already have their drinks.
If they're not for Table 11, which table ordered them?
- Is everything okay? - Yes.
(Yu Jin heard the news and stepped in.)
(She searches the dining area aimlessly.)
Is everything okay?
Yes, everything is very delicious.
Is there anything you need?
Has anything you ordered not been served?
- We're good. - We're good.
She's cute.
(The ades have nowhere to go.)
If they're not for Table 11, then where?
(The service team is confused.)
- Table 11 got everything. - Table 10 and 11.
I'll check with Table 10. You go check with Table 11.
I think I gave you the wrong table number. I'm sorry, Kyung Soo.
(Puppy goes on her second round of patrol.)
- You didn't get your ades, did you? - No, we didn't.
- We found them! - We have your ades right here.
(Here are your ades.)
We found them!
(They're finally served to the right table.)
(Table 10: 2 pomegranate ades, 2 yuzu ades)
(Table 10: Everything has been served.)
- Doh Kyung Soo! - Doh Kyung Soo!
(They're chanting the part-timer's name for some unknown reason.)
- Here's your ade. - Doh Kyung Soo!
Did you order two of these?
- No, we ordered just one. - No.
(Their carrot cake has already been served.)
- You ordered just 1? Okay. - I think it's for Table 11.
Table 11, has your carrot cake been served?
- No, it hasn't. - The carrot cake...
(They found the customers who ordered the carrot cake.)
(Table 11: 1 mint carrot cake)
(Shout "Doh Kyung Soo" when you're happy.)
- Doh Kyung Soo! - Please enjoy.
That went well. That was great.
(This is fun.)
(This is really fun.)
(They return with light hearts.)
It's totally over.
(What do you mean it's over?)
(The next customers enter.)
Hello. May I take your order now?
Yes, please. Can we have three beef burger combos...
- Yes, three beef burger combos. - and three cakes?
- Would you like three of those? - Yes, please.
Understood.
Can we swap the combo drinks for ades?
- Oh, gosh. What should we do? - It's beef.
(The new ordering trend)
(1 burger and 1 dessert per person)
They ordered three carrot cakes.
(Main Dish: 4 beef burgers, 1 shrimp burger, 1 rice cracker taco)
(Dessert: 4 carrot cakes, 2 pomegranate ades, 2 yuzu ades)
I'll make a glass of pomegranate ade and a glass of yuzu ade.
- One pomegranate and one yuzu. - One more beef burger.
(She pulls herself together and steps up to make the ades.)
- I'll make three cakes. - Three cakes...
- I'll make three cakes. - Okay.
- Young Ji, we can do this. - Yes, we can.
(She'll cook 4 beef patties at the same time.)
(She puts her whole heart into pressing the patty.)
The griddle is working beautifully today.
Three beef burgers are ready...
- for the same table. - Got it.
- Yes, it's out. - Then...
- let's serve the cakes too. - Okay.
- Will you serve the cakes too? - These are for Table 12.
- Table 12? - Yes.
- It's perfect. - I'll go first.
(Everything is ready for the table of 3.)
(It feels like something is missing.)
- Table 12, right? I'll go. - Yes.
- Then I'll... Oh, the shovels. - You forgot the shovels.
(The customers almost had to peck at their food like a crane.)
It was my first time making carrot cakes.
Thank you.
(With shovel spoons dug into the carrot cakes...)
- Okay. I'll take the ticket down. - Okay.
- Here's your food. - Thank you.
Here are the three beef burgers you ordered.
- Oh, no. I'm sorry. - That's okay.
- The shrimp burger is ready. - Yes, the shrimp burger is up.
- Two glasses of ade, and it's over. - Okay.
(Please give me a minute.)
- It's for Table 4. - Table 4.
- I'll go first. - Okay.
Thank you. I'll put it on here.
(Kyung Soo heads out with the ade.)
Thank you. Please enjoy. Oh, no. I'm sorry.
It looks delicious.
(The 1-burger-per-person table tastes the food.)
- I can just tell it's good. - It looks amazing.
(He finally takes his first bite of the burger.)
This is a whole new taste.
Indeed. Surprisingly, they go well together.
I want to buy this recipe.
What are you going to do with it?
If they hire me...
(While they talk about opening a new Space Rice Cake location...)
- Take your time with the menu... - Yes.
and let me know when you're ready to order.
Anything new on the menu today?
Yes, we're serving tacos today. It's a new menu item.
- It's called Uno, Dos, Tres, Taco. - Can we have one of those?
One taco.
One taco...
- Yes. - And...
The taco is a hit, Mimi.
- Is it? - The taco is selling really well.
I owe it all to the whole team.
- One taco is ready. - One taco is ready.
One more taco is up.
I think it's a great idea.
- It's good. - It's a great combination.
(- Nice. - Is it tasty?)
(Honestly, we think it's tasty.)
Kyung Soo...
- loves tacos. - That makes sense.
(Yes. Kyung Soo, who loves tacos, came up with the recipe.)
The taco looks pretty. I love the vibrant colors.
(Space Rice Cake's own unique rice cracker taco)
(But there is an obstacle.)
One, two,
three, four...
(Mimi is counting rice crackers.)
Five, six...
And 7. It's supposed to have 7 of them, right?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
(She's wrong.)
Why do I get so nervous every time I count?
- Mimi. - Yes?
Call me when you need to count.
One taco is up.
(She plates 7 rice crackers for the next taco dish.)
(Then, she tops them with the stir-fried beef.)
There are six rice crackers there.
(The cameraman says she has only six rice crackers.)
You need one more rice cracker. One rice cracker is missing.
(What? There's no way.)
I swear, I counted right.
(She really is missing one.)
(She quickly adds one.)
That was a close call.
But I was sure I counted seven.
I think I should go back to elementary school.
The beef burger is up too.
I feel bad about myself.
(Reason for re-enrollment: Self-loathing over a rice cracker)
- The colors are great. - Indeed.
(The Guam Elementary School graduate did a good job despite everything.)
(Thank you, sir.)
Here's your food.
(Mimi's taco made with a little help from the cameraman is served.)
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Here's the rice cracker taco you ordered.
(How does it taste?)
(Impressed)
It tastes like a tortilla when you eat it.
The moment you bite into it.
- It's good. - Yes.
(Fortunately, the customers give positive feedback.)
(Right then, a group of customers finished their food.)
- Did you enjoy the food? - Yes, we did.
What was your favorite?
- The shrimp burger. - The shrimp burger?
(Everyone likes the shrimp burger.)
- We didn't leave the food... - Oh, right.
because it wasn't good.
- Because you were full? - No, it was because...
- The rice crackers vanished. - They vanished.
- Because of the moisture... - Oh, I see.
- The rice crackers disappeared. - They melted due to the moisture.
- The rice crackers disappeared? - They melted away...
- They melted from the moisture. - They melted away.
We ended up with a lot of leftover toppings because of that.
- Oh, no. - That...
Thank you for your feedback. Go home safely.
- Go home safely. - Thank you.
- Ahk. - Goodbye.
- Go home safely. - Goodbye.
The rice crackers...
(The urgent meeting about the tacos)
- What should we do about it? - We should serve it first.
We can't serve them separately from the toppings.
Should we serve it with ten rice crackers?
I guess it's the moisture from the toppings.
(Director Doh became serious after hearing the taco feedback.)
(Giggling)
(Director Doh is thinking hard.)
- Or we can do this. - Okay.
Since the customers eat them together anyway,
let's arrange the rice crackers around the rim of the plate...
- and put the meat in the center. - Shall we? That's a good idea.
(Here's Director Doh's solution.)
(1. Serve more rice crackers and place them around the rim.)
(2. Pile the toppings in the center.)
(Minimizing contact with the toppings...)
(will keep the rice crackers crunchy!)
(Rice cracker taco version 2 is now available.)
(Chef Mimi starts making the taco.)
I'll try out...
Director Doh's...
idea.
(Placing the rice crackers around the rim of the plate)
Nine... Okay.
Just as Director Doh said,
his way leaves the center empty.
(Stir-fried beef)
(Avocados)
(Tomato salsa)
- This is better, right? - Yes, it's way better.
(Both Director Doh and Chef Mimi are happy with the result.)
(Adding Parmigiano cheese that will give extra flavor...)
(and crushed pepper)
- This is better. - Yes, it's good.
I did it just as you told me to.
(The 1st plate of rice cracker taco version 2 is ready!)
(It's done! Isn't it easy?)
- Head Chef, I have a question. - Yes?
Aren't you going...
- to a Chinese restaurant later? - Yes.
- A Chinese restaurant? - A Chinese restaurant.
It's only a five-minute walk.
Do you want to take a car or walk?
But I have to...
go home after this shift.
- No. - But you're working in the evening.
You said earlier that you were staying all day.
- Come on. - Right? You're lying, aren't you?
Kyung Soo, what are you talking about?
Things are running smoothly right now thanks to you.
- That's right. - Right.
- It'll be very busy tonight. - Right.
You should be really grateful...
to the servers.
(Many thoughts behind his expression)
- Yes, I'm very grateful to them. - The servers.
I think we only need...
one person in the kitchen.
(The head chef is speechless.)
- Kyung Soo, why don't you run... - You have to work with us.
- the kitchen by yourself tonight? - Yes.
The four of us can serve.
- I was just... - You're being ridiculous.
throwing the idea out there.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Would you like to order? - Yes.
- You're so pretty. - Thank you.
You aren't real, are you? Aren't you 2D?
- I'm real. - Are you?
We have an order.
- Yes? - One yuzu ade, one pizza,
one taco, and one beef burger.
- Okay. - Got it.
One pizza, one taco,
two carrot cakes, one yuzu ade,
one shrimp burger, two pomegranate ades, and one beef burger.
- Right now, - Yes?
we have two pieces of dough left.
That will be fine.
Shall I make some more dough?
No, Young Ji. It will be fine.
We already made 12, so we need to get 10 orders.
Orders of what?
- Pizza? - Yes.
(The head chef looks deep in thought.)
(12 dough pieces prepared in total)
- And... - The dough got stuck together.
- Oh, this... - Right.
(7 pieces of dough have been sold.)
(Prepped dough: 12, torn dough: 2, dough sold: 7)
(Remaining dough: 3)
If you have time to make more dough, you can go ahead.
It's totally doable.
(One dough piece disappeared.)
(This morning)
(One piece of dough went straight into the inferno.)
(Taking advantage of the chaos)
(By moving swiftly and stealthily,)
(she covered her tracks perfectly.)
No one knows.
(Just like that,)
(Young Ji got away with her crime.)
We have three pizzas left to make.
- Three pizzas? - Shall I make more dough?
- Yu Jin. - Yes?
I can stretch another dough right now.
Yu Jin, shall I make some dough?
No, I think we have enough.
So we'll be fine.
(2 remaining dough pieces)
(Unaware of Young Ji's secret, she starts making pizzas.)
(Sprinkling on plenty of cheese)
(Adding a blush of red on top)
(They go into the oven.)
(0 remaining dough pieces)
(While the pizzas get baked)
Welcome. Nice to meet you.
Thank you for coming.
One supreme and...
Too much rice cake in a burger
(Doing her best until the end)
(Thank you, ma'am.)
(The team members look at her with a lot of respect.)
- One pizza. - Ghost pepper pizza.
Unfortunately...
Is it not available?
It's sold out.
(Disappointed)
- Then... - Do you want me to check again?
(Also feeling disappointed, she checks again.)
Wasn't there a pizza in the order Yu Jin just called out?
- Yes. - We're out of pizza now, right?
Right.
I have some bad news.
- Shall I make some pizza? - It's sold out.
(Murmuring)
- Can you make a pizza? - Shall I make one?
Shall I make a pizza?
- Pizza? Do you want to? - Should I make that?
Can you do it?
Do I just make the dough?
As long as you make the dough, I'll do the rest.
- One pizza? As long as you make... - I'll take the order.
- I'll take the order. - One pizza?
One pizza.
We'll make the dough and prepare it for you.
Thank you.
(Dough Kyung Soo makes 1 more piece of dough.)
We have one shrimp burger,
one pizza,
one taco, and two cakes.
(Getting the dough ready right away)
- The temperature... - Is it not going up?
- Do I make it with one of these? - Yes.
(He grabs one dough ball.)
Mimi.
(Drizzling on some oil and placing it on)
One, two.
Turn on the heat, let it soften a little,
and just press it down. It'll turn out like that.
(He plans to stretch the dough on the pan.)
I'm 100 percent sure.
(You're making the dough without a rolling pin?)
Six.
Mimi.
(Firing up the burner)
Nine. Oh, my.
(Glancing)
Having you beside me makes my heart flutter.
- What? - It's nice.
Are you starting it?
(Kyung Soo sparked a flame in the wrong place.)
- What are you doing? - It's great.
Doesn't Mimi look like Bonobono today?
- So I look like Bonobono... - That's hilarious.
because there's a man around.
I like that.
- She's so funny. - Mimi, is that what this is about?
He casually picked this up right beside me.
And my heart skipped a beat.
That's amazing.
(Eyeing him eagerly)
He's so sexy.
Mimi.
(He came to make dough but ended up hopelessly entangled.)
(Spreading the dough thinly right on the pan)
(Once it's spread out evenly enough,)
(it's time to flip it over.)
Do I just flip this?
- The dough is ready. - Okay.
It actually became crunchy.
(A subtle battle of nerves)
- What? - What?
Kyung Soo.
- Yes? - You're busy. Never mind.
Kyung Soo isn't busy.
- He looks busy. - I have to do this now.
He's not busy. I'll take care of it.
(Suddenly, Kyung Soo gets busy.)
- Ask him for help. - Then...
Is it okay?
One yuzu and two pomegranates, please.
(He goes back to his original spot.)
- We'd like to pay. - That's right.
- Again... - Please take good care of it.
Thank you so much...
- for waiting and understanding. - You're welcome.
- It's 33.30 dollars. - Okay.
I don't think I can make four.
- Enjoy your food. - Thank you.
- You're so handsome. - Thank you.
Yu Jin, I'll make one of the pizzas.
Be careful, everyone.
(Taking care of the pizza for Yu Jin who's busy)
Young Ji, today's dough came out really well.
It's very...
But I didn't make that dough.
- It was Director Doh who made it. - I see.
He's good at making dough.
(On top of the dough made by Dough Kyung Soo)
(Placing fragrant basil)
(Once you sprinkle on some cheese, it's ready.)
(When the last pizza is made)
- Hello. - Hello.
Here's your food.
(The part-timer serves it.)
Here's your pizza.
(The Last Table: 2 mint carrot cakes)
- It's Mimi. - Five?
(Mimi starts cleaning up.)
(However...)
- It's not cut at all. - No.
I think it's cut.
No, it's not cut.
- Just in case... - Eun Ji, when Mimi gets back,
could you ask if anyone is having trouble eating the pizza?
If anyone is having trouble eating the pizza?
If everything is okay?
There's a pizza that just went out.
To which table?
What's wrong with the pizza?
Please ask them.
- Hello. - Did you enjoy the food?
(The pizza that I just served)
The food is delicious.
- Thank you. - Thank you. Enjoy your food.
Thank you.
- A pizza that just went out? - I'll take the two...
Is it because it's not cut?
It wasn't sliced.
I have a feeling that it wasn't cut.
- No way. - It wasn't sliced.
(An eyewitness account)
- I guess it wasn't cut. - What?
- Pizza? - Pizza.
- Should I go and check? - Who's in charge of making pizza?
- We need to ask Mimi. - Mimi.
Go upstairs and ask Mimi...
- Didn't you cut it? - if she didn't cut...
- Which table was it? - Just go and ask Mimi.
(Mimi just happens to be cleaning next to the unsliced pizza.)
Mimi.
(Mimi, what happened?)
I don't think...
the pizza that just went out was cut.
- Which table is it? - Pizza?
- It's that table. - That one?
The one across from us.
Is it not cut?
Is it usually cut?
Is the pizza sliced?
- It wasn't sliced, was it? - Right?
How could this happen?
- I know. - It's okay.
This is an unbelievable mistake.
- We apologize. - Gosh, it's okay.
- I'll cut it for you. - Thankfully, they have a knife.
- I'll cut it for you. - I brought a knife.
They already cut it into a few pieces.
Did you slice it yourselves so it'd be easier to eat?
- Thank you. - Enjoy your food.
We'll handle this properly.
- Ahk. Go downstairs. - Ahk.
- What do we do? - Go downstairs.
Let's go downstairs.
I bowed my head in apology.
Should we offer them something on the house?
Was that the table with four women?
The one who ordered...
- It was a table of four women. - That's right.
They asked me about my performance.
They said they couldn't afford it and asked if they could see it.
I told them, "Save up your money and come back."
- Do it for free. - I should've done it for them.
(Lee Eun Ji's performance for 99,999 dollars)
(The most expensive item on Space Rice Cake's menu)
I heard that it was 100,000 dollars.
What do we do? We can't afford it.
(Customers who inquired about the 100,000-dollar item)
In that case, you have to work hard and save up.
(She advised them to save up 100,000 dollars.)
(Spinning)
- Thank you, everyone. - Thank you.
- It was a mini performance. - Thank you.
(She only gave a mini performance for free.)
- A free performance? - Do a free performance.
A free performance to apologize for not slicing the pizza?
Should I do "I Am the Best" or "Fire?"
- How about we perform together? - All of us.
Let's do "I Am the Best."
(A group performance for compensation)
(With the leader who's nervous before her first performance)
What if we give them indigestion?
(The little ones follow close behind.)
(All serious for no reason)
(Feeling uncomfortable already)
Gosh, they startled me.
(The leader and her crew march across the hall.)
- To our guests at Table 13, - Hello.
we sincerely apologize.
When you asked us about a performance,
we suggested you save up and come back.
But it turns out we sent out your pizza without slicing it.
- For that... - It's totally unacceptable.
We sincerely...
- apologize. - We're sorry.
While you enjoy your meal,
like a dinner show,
we'll put on a small performance for you.
(A performance of apology)
(Leader Lee Eun Ji, Second Kim Mi Hyun, Third Lee Young Ji,)
(Youngest An Yu Jin, Special Guest Doh Kyung Soo)
Five, six, seven, eight.
(Singing)
(An opening song nobody agreed on)
(It's their first gig, so the members aren't used to it.)
(The leader is in her element.)
(A performance for one table only)
(We sent out an unsliced pizza. Oh, my gosh.)
(The end of the performance)
Once again, we bow our heads...
- in apology. - We apologize.
Honestly, it turned out for the better.
Thank you so much.
- Enjoy your food. - It's 90,000 dollars' worth...
of compensation.
- Enjoy your food. - Excuse me,
- Enjoy your food. - but is the pizza usually sliced?
- Mimi. - Ours wasn't cut.
This table too.
Three, two, one. Let's go.
(Quickly starting their 2nd performance)
(There's absolute chaos.)
(His energy is completely drained.)
(They seem to enjoy giving their performance of apology.)
(Hey!)
- Once again, we bow our heads... - Thank you.
- in apology. - We apologize.
- We're very sorry. - We apologize.
(The group performance tour comes to an end.)
We apologize.
I just asked out of curiosity.
I didn't know what the problem was.
Look how we cut it.
(The pizza still looks ridiculous.)
That was amazing.
I wonder...
who's in charge of the pizza.
I'm actually grateful.
(They even got to enjoy a live show.)
- It's 100,000 dollars' worth. - I know.
- It's more than 100,000 dollars. - Exactly.
Gosh, our lunch service is finally over.
- Well done, everyone. - Oh, my.
I'm okay.
- But you don't look okay at all. - I'm really okay.
(She's too exhausted to even stand.)
Let's have something to drink.
(Refreshing and fizzy)
(Quenching their thirst with a sweet drink)
It hits the spot when you're exhausted.
- What do you think, Mimi? - It's very refreshing.
I can enjoy every last drop of it.
This is the best.
(Drinking)
(Bubbly and refreshing just like Yu Jin)
It'd go really well...
- It'd be a perfect match. - with slightly greasy food.
It's 30 percent lower in sugar and calories.
- That's great. - That explains it.
(After enjoying a sweet break)
I'm curious about this too.
Don't look. I'll tell you over there.
Go back to your seat.
(It's time to tally up the sales again.)
- I'll announce the results. - Five hundred?
Do you have any guesses?
How about 550 dollars?
I think it's 600 dollars.
(How about you?)
Is it 570 dollars?
We didn't have many customers today. How about 400 dollars?
(Drumroll, please.)
(Getting the crowd hyped up)
(How much did they make during lunch?)
We made 1,050 dollars.
How did we earn so much?
We sold so many pizzas.
We said we were sold out,
but we still made more dough and sold more pizzas.
Well done.
- We did an awesome job. - We made 1,000 dollars.
We made 1,050 dollars.
That's incredible.
(The applause just keeps coming.)
How did this happen?
Kyung Soo, well done.
(It's my pleasure.)
Did you pay for your drink?
(The head chef chimes in with a complaint.)
I guess you didn't.
How much is it?
It's two dollars.
- It's two dollars. - Okay.
Two dollars and the bun that you ruined earlier.
What else?
- Did he ruin a bun too? - What else?
He burnt a piece of dough.
How much is that?
- Hey, listen. - What?
Let's not be too hard on Kyung Soo.
- This guide to taking orders... - Why?
that Kyung Soo wrote himself...
- at the counter is very touching. - What is it?
It makes me feel sad...
and incredibly grateful.
"As spicy as Buldak."
(Just in case the customer can't handle the spices...)
Kyung Soo wrote it all down.
(He carefully noted it down.)
It breaks my heart to see something like this.
If he helps out tonight,
should we increase his hourly wage?
Pay him more?
- How would you feel about that? - Do you have a rate in mind?
So far, I worked 4 hours... Did I work 3 hours?
- Because... - In the morning,
he started at 9:30am.
- But he was our instructor then. - From 9:30am?
- From 9:30am. - I prepared the tacos this morning.
- Really? - We should count his hours...
starting at 9:30am.
- From 9:30am to 3:30pm, - Right.
- he worked six hours. - Yes.
He'll work from 5pm to 9pm, so that's 4 hours.
- The total is ten hours. My gosh. - Yes.
Then let's make it two dollars per hour.
Two dollars per hour?
How about ten dollars? Let's be generous.
I was going to start at 20 dollars.
- Twenty dollars? - Twenty dollars?
Then we have to pay the part-timer 200 dollars.
No way. We won't be able to buy SK Hynix stock.
What if we pay him 200 dollars...
and have him work...
on the second floor all night?
Make him work nonstop?
- I'm sorry. - We can get our money's worth.
- That sounds good. - I'm sorry.
- Let's pay him 200 dollars. - Right.
- For one day... - We can ask him...
- to make dough nonstop. - That sounds good.
If we make 2,000 dollars in sales tonight,
paying him 200 dollars will be worth it.
That's a great deal for us.
Let's give him 250 dollars...
and make him work all night going up and down.
We'll make him prepare 30 pieces of dough.
If he makes dough and works on the second floor,
paying him 200 dollars...
We'll be really generous...
and pay you 250 dollars.
Did you say 250 dollars? Okay.
(Wage negotiations are done.)
Is there a contract?
There's a clause that I want to add.
Can I read the clauses before I sign?
Of course.
If I don't like what I see,
- can I just go home? - Of course.
- You can't go home. - Really?
- You can't go home. - She said, "Of course."
You were employed by the HQ,
- Right. - so that's a separate matter.
(Something feels fishy.)
Please wait. They're in the pantry.
Can you tell me what you want?
I'd like him to serve on the second floor.
- That's what... - We shouldn't add that.
- We can take care of that... - What do you want him to do?
I want him to make 30 pieces of dough.
- Okay, write that down. - That sounds good.
- All right. - It's a contract.
And frying tater tots.
(An awkward chuckle)
I'd like him to check if the pizzas are sliced.
- You should do that instead. - It should be checked.
- You should do it. - You do it, Mimi.
- But I... - You can do it yourself.
I have no memory. I'm sorry.
(The contract drafting begins.)
- We can write about the dough. - Minimum 30.
He has to make dough.
Making a minimum of 30 to a maximum of 40.
Let's do that.
(Whispering)
From 30... No, like this.
- Minimum? - Like this.
Right.
Hurry up and give it to me. What are you guys doing?
- Just... - Just say that it's a requirement.
- It's done. - Okay.
(The contract is completed.)
(All he has to do is sign it.)
The payment is 250 dollars.
(At first glance, it looks like an ordinary contract.)
"Pizza dough..."
How many is it? Is it 30 or 40?
- Minimum 30. - Minimum 30.
Maximum 40.
(Something still feels off.)
(Hurry up and sign it.)
Thirty?
- Okay. - We'll help you out.
- You won't be making 40 yourself. - Of course not.
We're doing it together. Got it?
- He signed it. - He did it.
Yes!
(The deal with Doh Kyung Soo is official.)
Did you read it carefully?
I don't think he read the bottom part.
What?
- It's nothing. - It's nothing.
- It's okay. - Everything was written on it.
- It was written on it. - It's nothing.
- Thirty or forty... - Thank you so much.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Honesty.
- Humility. - Humility.
- Ahk. - Ahk.
- Take a break. - Take a break.
Let's go and eat.
(The truth is...)
(A secret toxic clause was hidden inside.)
(Unlimited serving on the 2nd floor)
(He tries to look over the contract again.)
Right. What did you write?
It's nothing.
Thirty to forty dough pieces.
We did a good job writing it, right?
(He can't help but feel like he's been played.)
- He has no idea. - Well done.
Hide it somewhere far away.
He couldn't see it because I was holding it like this.
I thought so.
(It's time for lunch!)
We can all share it.
Stir-fried jjajangmyeon and jjamppong.
Since you're making 250 dollars today,
- eat as much as you want. - Eat a lot.
- Okay. - Eat a lot.
Did you promise to pay him 250 dollars?
Yes, for today's work.
- We gave him a lot of work. - We wrote a contract.
They told me to make 30 pieces of dough.
- Actually, it's 40. - It's 40.
From 30 to 40.
- Right. - Maximum of 40.
(The Earth Arcaders are strict about their contract.)
Shouldn't we get tangsuyuk?
We ordered it.
- And chili shrimp. - And chili shrimp.
You can order whatever you want.
You should eat more. Eat a lot.
You'll be doing a tough job later.
He'll be doing a tough job later?
(For tough labor in the evening,)
(he makes his choice carefully.)
- It's very expensive. - Did you pick it?
- The food is really good here. - My goodness.
- Yu Jin. - Gosh.
Shall I separate it?
No, that's fine.
- Can we get some scissors? - Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you for the food.
- Bon appetit. Thank you. - Bon appetit.
Do you pour the sauce or dip it?
- I don't mind either way. - Me neither.
When we share it, it doesn't matter.
That's right.
- Kyung Soo has a preference. - Do you dip it in?
- Yes. - What do you prefer?
- Do you dip it in? - Do you dip it in?
- Or do you pour it? - You can pour half of it.
- You like to dip it in? - Yes.
- Pour half of it. - That sounds good.
- Pour half of it. - Pour half of it.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you.
(A bite of the chili shrimp)
(Humming)
- It's so good. - It's delicious.
- Is it good? - Yes.
(Very satisfied)
Since we have a part-timer,
- we get to eat out. - I'm hungry.
- Is it your first time eating out? - It is.
- Including our time in Goheung, - It's hot.
isn't it our first time?
- We're like prisoners. - I know.
There's a ton of good food in Goheung.
We couldn't eat anything there.
- I know. - We only had tteokbokki.
- We really did. - It was terrible.
We couldn't eat anything else.
(Food always tastes best when someone else makes it.)
Young Ji, Kyung Soo, how did you become close?
- "Small Girl." - Right, "Small Girl."
It was all the rage.
Shouldn't you call him a senior, Young Ji?
Well...
Young Ji calls me...
- Mister. - Mr. Kyung Soo?
- Do you call anyone informally? - I do.
- You do? - You do.
But you call Kyung Soo formally because you don't like him?
No, but I don't bother.
(Nobody knows the rules behind her addressing someone informally.)
The days in Goheung were the romantic age.
- Yes, it was the best. - I agree.
The age of innocence and romance.
We'd discuss the menu names and laugh.
- Our Chestnut Tyranno. - Chestnut Tyranno!
For the dinner business, can you do this, Kyung Soo?
- Too much rice cake in a burger - He must do it, of course.
I think he wants to do it.
- Yu Jin, teach him. - What is it?
(Embarrassed)
You need to do this when you serve.
Let me teach you.
- Too much rice cake in a burger. - Rice cake.
- That's the name of the burger. - Too much rice cake in a burger?
- Ask what it is. - Too much rice cake in a burger...
Too much rice cake in a burger
- It's too... - Hold on.
(It's too much for Yu Jin.)
He's right in front of you.
He's too close. Like this...
- You're so mean. - I know.
- You don't even pretend to smile. - Please smile.
- Eun Ji, please show him. - Kyung Soo, you should smile.
That's not nice.
Too much rice cake in a burger You need to do it like this.
- I need to do that? - Yes.
- That's the name. - You need to do it.
- It was in the contract. - People will ask.
The contract says I need to sing "too much rice cake in a burger?"
It's really in the contract. Check it later.
It's really in the contract.
- You get paid 250 dollars. - Let's go back and practice.
Yes.
There's a dance move too. I'll teach you later.
Dance? It's Doh Kyung Soo you're talking about.
- I know. - He's Doh Kyung Soo.
- An all-rounder. - He's a great singer and a dancer.
- It's exactly 4pm. - We need to go.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
(But...)
- A dough battle? - I'm on.
I'm so on.
We'll battle with a frying pan each.
- We need to make the dough. - Let's do it.
(They agree to a dough battle on the way back.)
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
- Will you really make 30? - Yes.
(There's a strange tension between the two.)
Okay.
It's a battle.
(Dividing the sticky rice before the battle)
Why don't we have a match where whoever gets the weight...
closer to 250g wins?
- Okay. - This is crazy.
- Just one round? - One round.
- Good luck, Young Ji. Beat him. - Hold on.
(A warm-up game: Weighing sticky rice)
I got it.
I'm sorry, but I really got it.
I'm definitely closer.
No more changing.
I'm done changing.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Weigh it.
(Young Ji's sticky rice is weighed first.)
- It's 257g. - It's 257g.
It's 257g.
(That's very close with just 7g difference.)
(What about Kyung Soo's sticky rice?)
I won.
(Kyung Soo's sticky rice is 296g, exceeding by 46g.)
- It's that heavy? - It is.
(The head chef shows him who's the boss.)
This is why...
You can't get 250g right, so don't divide it. I'll do it.
(Immediately acting cocky)
(She's just adorable.)
(Grinning)
I told you that you need to put this first.
(The quarrel looks familiar.)
Are you filming the "Small Girl" music video?
- This is so... - What are you doing?
- I think I watched this scene. - Exactly.
Kyung Soo, then what's the prize for the winner?
Will the loser grant the winner's wish?
That's right.
"That's right?"
(She's funny.)
Did you make a bet because you want to spend time with him?
- I didn't suggest it. - You're adorable.
Coat it thoroughly.
(Changing the subject)
One, two, three, four...
I want Kyung Soo to win and make a wish like this.
"Stop calling me Mr. Kyung Soo."
"Call me Kyung Soo." You know what I mean?
(She pretends that she didn't hear her.)
See? Young Ji normally reacts to whatever we say,
but she can't now because she's shy.
Because you're speaking nonsense.
This is so fun.
In "My Lovely Sam Soon," they fight in the kitchen like this.
That's how Hyun Bin and Sam Soon fall in love.
I know what you mean.
- While they're baking, right? - That's it.
It's like a scene in a teenage comic.
You're really good at pretending you can't hear anything.
(Chuckling)
Kyung Soo is enjoying this situation.
You should too, Young Ji.
(The 24-year-old girl feels shy.)
How can you stick this to the box?
It's 14, 16, 18, 20, 21...
Let's go. There are 22.
The person who finishes 11 wins.
Kyung Soo. What wish will you make if you win?
Me?
What wish should I make?
Her calling you casually.
Yes, do that.
Hey.
Kyung Soo is so good at flirting. That's a crime.
- It makes your heart flutter. - That's a crime.
Young Ji, what wish will you make if you win?
I'll make him work for free today.
If Young Ji wins,
- he'll work unpaid. - Unpaid.
No wage.
Here we go.
- Hold on. - What?
- If I win, - Yes.
pay me double the wage.
- So 500 dollars? - Yes.
Why is he changing his words?
What are you doing?
- Why did you suggest a match? - Young Ji.
- What did he say, 500 dollars? - Are you confident?
Double the wage. If I lose, my wage will be gone.
You said you wanted her to call you casually.
I've changed my mind.
Do what you want, Young Ji.
- Let's do it. - Okay.
- Young Ji, don't do it. - She has a mouth of terror.
Let's go.
You can do it, MOT!
(The dough battle starts.)
(If Young Ji wins, Kyung Soo will work unpaid.)
(If Kyung Soo wins, he'll get double the wage.)
Ready, go.
- It's really "Small Girl." - "Small Girl," right?
This is no joke.
(Kyung Soo's zone, Young Ji's zone)
They just wanted to do something together.
Don't touch mine.
(Squashing)
(Cheating as soon as she starts)
Don't you feel hot?
(Silent)
Why did you turn off the fire? Young Ji.
Stop playing dirty.
(In a rush all by herself)
If it doesn't look like dough, it doesn't count.
How could that ever happen?
- How can it not look like dough? - It can.
This isn't dough.
You're done for.
(Tattered)
How did you make it like this?
You just do it.
(The difference in quality is significant.)
(Pressing)
Stop it.
- Excuse me. - How did you do it?
How did he do it?
- You need to have a kind soul. - You should've taught me first.
How can you go ahead and do it yourself?
It says 30 in the contract, but I cut it down to 20.
Speaking of contract, many dramas in the 2000s...
were about contract dating.
"My Lovely Sam Soon" was about contract dating too.
In the end, they actually fall in love.
(Struggling)
Why does mine have a hole in the middle?
(Staring)
- You press it outward. - Yes.
- What am I supposed to do? - Spread out the thick part.
Don't just push it out from the middle.
(He puts the competition behind and teaches her the tips.)
Hold on. Goodness.
(Golden brown and in perfect shape)
I've completed one.
(Young Ji: 0, Kyung Soo: 1)
You're amazing, Kyung Soo!
- Good luck, Kyung Soo! - I can do it.
You can do it!
- His voice changed. - Just now...
When he said that,
- It was nice, right? Teen romance. - it was a teen romance vibe.
- A basketball prodigy vibe. - A basketball prodigy.
What's this?
(Young Ji's dough still hasn't cooked.)
- You knew, didn't you? - I had no idea.
(Young Ji's burner was off the whole time.)
(Kyung Soo has completed his second dough.)
- You can do it, Kyung Soo. - I can do it.
(Squealing)
(Eun Ji's heart flutters.)
(Young Ji: 0, Kyung Soo: 2)
I've already won. You didn't even finish one.
This is my third one.
- Excuse me, everyone. - Yes.
My 500-dollar wage is confirmed.
Why?
I've won.
- Not yet. - Okay.
(Young Ji's first dough is finally complete.)
I won't lose.
- You can do it, Young Ji. - I can do it.
(But Kyung Soo picks up the pace.)
(What should I do?)
Young Ji, it isn't over until it's over.
Young Ji, don't get hurt. Watch your hand.
(Young Ji catches up quickly.)
- It's 2 to 2. - No.
Then?
- It's 4 to 2. - It's not 4 to 2.
- Is it really 4 to 2? - It's 4 to 2.
This is impossible.
Oh, dear.
Okay!
Player Lee Young Ji has burned her dough. One eliminated.
Lee Young Ji, do you have 500 dollars?
What will we do with her?
- The burning smell is so strong. - Young Ji, open the window.
(So many malicious comments for burning the dough)
Why don't we conclude it as my win and I cook the rest?
Young Ji?
- He's provoking her. - He's provoking her.
- You can't get triggered like this. - She's already lost.
I'll do it, Young Ji.
(Nodding)
- Young Ji, just let him do it. - You acknowledge your defeat?
My wage is 500 dollars.
Five hundred dollars?
Young Ji.
- Seriously. - What's this?
I told you not to do it if you weren't confident.
Exactly. Five hundred dollars...
Do you know how many times...
I need to frequent the 2nd floor to earn 500 dollars?
(She has nothing to say.)
Young Ji, just help me with this.
- Do this now. - Come here.
(Demoted to moving carrot cakes)
Kyung Soo,
is your wish really getting 500 dollars?
I think it makes no sense.
- What? - You've lost.
In what?
You lost the 250g match.
Should we check the VAR?
You lost that, so we're even.
Then 300 dollars.
(The part-timer isn't easily swayed.)
What's that?
If you want it so badly, have it your way.
Yes, 300 dollars.
(Negotiated to 300 dollars)
It's okay. He just needs to work that much more.
(Getting their money's worth by firing up every burner)
Now that Kyung Soo is here today,
Kwak Cheol Yong doesn't appear.
- You're right. - I miss Cheol Yong.
Kwak Cheol Yong hasn't appeared once today.
Cheol Yong, where are you? I'm Jeong Hye.
I'm here. Where are you, Cheol Yong? Here?
Have you seen Cheol Yong?
I haven't.
Cheol Yong, why won't you...
show yourself today?
I haven't seen him today either.
He isn't around today.
In the end, he abandoned me.
Jeong Hye.
(Cheol Yong!)
(Cheol Yong finally lets his voice be heard.)
Cheol Yong.
(Sobbing)
I can hear your voice, Cheol Yong.
(I don't want you to see my pathetic self.)
Where is he? I heard his voice from here.
Cheol Yong?
(Crying)
- Jeong Hye. - Cheol Yong.
Why are you...
Cheol Yong, why are you hiding here?
(Please leave me alone.)
(Cheol Yong and Jeong Hye's tear-jerking reunion)
- Jeong Hye. - Yes.
- Cheer up, Cheol Yong. - Let's kiss passionately later.
You always say that but don't do anything.
If you work well without getting hurt,
I'll kiss you like you say.
(Sure, Jeong Hye.)
It's 5:30pm now.
- Okay. I'll turn it around. - Okay.
- Go ahead. - Let's go.
(Space Rice Cake, 2nd Branch)
(The dinner business starts.)
I turned it around.
- Let's do this. - Thanks.
(The kitchen is reorganizing.)
(The ade zone)
(The cake zone)
This is smart.
- Right? - Make more.
- More? - More.
(Laughing)
- I'll make more. - More. You can do it.
(As per the director's instruction,)
(she prepares more ade.)
(16 glasses prepared)
(Ketchup)
(Mustard)
(Young Ji prepares the sauces.)
(Mimi prepares the dough.)
(And Kyung Soo takes over the stove.)
(Young Ji's face looks odd.)
(A man grilling the dough skillfully)
The dough looks amazing.
You're really good.
You can do it, Kyung Soo.
- I can do it. - You can do it.
Kyung Soo, don't get hurt.
(He doesn't know how to respond.)
(She's envious.)
(She gets herself together and grills rice cake bun.)
Young Ji, that looks incredible.
Right?
I can't flip it because the rice cake is hard.
- Oh, I can. - Amazing.
(Zooming in on Kyung Soo)
(Zooming in on Young Ji's rice cake buns)
Why are you going back and forth between me and him?
- Sorry? - Why are you going back and forth?
Just film me and only me.
(Snorting)
(I'm sorry.)
(Meanwhile, two parties of customers enter.)
Welcome.
- Are you two different parties? - Yes.
Have a look at the pop-up zone.
- Okay. - Thanks.
I see.
- Pomegranate ade. - Pomegranate ade, got it.
- Here you go. - Thanks. Do we go up?
Yes. Thank you.
We're out of this.
We're out of receipt paper.
(While Eun Ji refills the receipt paper...)
(Pondering)
From what I remember,
there's 1 taco, 1 beef, and 1 shrimp.
(Distrusting)
- Are you sure? - Yes.
When the bill is printed...
And pomegranate ade...
and yuzu ade, one of each.
I'll check when the bill is printed.
I'm 100 percent sure.
- This time... - Kyung Soo, please check this.
Okay. Table One.
One beef burger, one shrimp burger, and one taco.
(Table 1: 1 beef burger combo, 1 shrimp burger combo,)
(1 rice cracker taco, 1 mint carrot cake)
(What about drinks?)
And one pomegranate ade...
- And yuzu ade. - and one yuzu ade.
- Answer. - Yes.
(Laughing)
You're supposed to reply.
Young Ji, the tables have turned...
(Meanwhile, on the second floor...)
- Where are you, Dad? - It snapped.
- Until there... - Really?
(Calling Dad who couldn't come)
We saw Doh Kyung Soo.
(Chuckling)
(She can't breathe because her heart is racing fast.)
I can't say anything...
He has such big eyes.
So it's scary when he stares at you.
Even when I'm here,
I can feel him staring at me from this side.
It's really scary.
(She isn't wrong.)
(He's monitoring her closely.)
(Glancing)
(Sliding quietly)
The first group didn't order a pizza.
But we made almost 20 dough pieces.
- Go and tell them to order it. - Pizza...
They didn't order a pizza.
(Expressing his anxiety here and there)
- They didn't order a pizza. - They'll...
They'll order one soon.
- Here's the next order. - Okay.
One pizza,
and 2 ades, 1 for each flavor.
(Order Status: Beef burger, shrimp burger, rice cracker taco,)
(beef burger, shrimp burger, rice cracker taco, pizza)
(Pouring sparkling water into the prepped glasses)
(Sticking the straw in)
- Eun Ji. - Yes?
Recommend pizza to the customers.
Recommend pizza? Got it.
We have a 300-dollar loss.
We need to make up for the loss.
(He's here too.)
It looks delicious.
(She finishes the taco under pressure.)
- This is for Table 1. - Yes, Table 1.
Cross off the rice cracker taco for Table One.
(He marks the dishes that are served.)
When will the shrimp and beef be ready?
- In three minutes. - Okay.
- We need one cake. - Okay.
(Under Director Doh's management,)
(the dishes are prepared quickly.)
(She takes the shrimp patty out and starts to assemble a burger.)
(Next, beef patty!)
One beef burger and one shrimp burger.
I'll serve beef and shrimp burgers.
Okay.
- How's the food? - It's good.
- Here's your cake. - Thank you.
- Enjoy your food. - Is this the cake?
- Yes. - It's cute.
The food is served quickly.
(All the food has been served for Table 1.)
They ordered a pizza.
(Placing chorizo on cheese)
(Finishing it off with button mushrooms!)
(It heads straight into the preheated oven.)
(Mimi is stir-frying beef with all her might.)
(It's turning delicious.)
(Pouring a generous amount of beef onto rice crackers.)
One scoop.
(Avocado and tomato salsa on top of it)
(Finishing it off with parmigiano)
- Enjoy your food. - Thanks.
I can serve them together.
You ordered a beef burger, right?
- Pizza will be served soon. - Thank you.
(After serving the food,)
(he has nothing to do.)
Why does it feel so relaxing?
Is it because we prepared everything in advance?
Isn't it much easier with this prepared?
The ades were prepared in advance.
(They're preparing everything in advance now.)
That was really smart of you.
We should've done this sooner.
(The last dish, the pizza, is ready too.)
Ghost pepper pizza.
Margherita, looking tasty.
(It's becoming more delicious thanks to the comedian's hard work.)
The new part-timer Doh Kyung Soo is here today.
I'm off.
Good luck.
(Enjoying herself)
Everything is served.
I'm so happy.
I feel good.
It's just the beginning.
I don't know how long this happiness will last.
I don't know either. I feel nervous.
Everything is served.
Isn't it really relaxing?
(And that makes him rather worried.)
- Goodness. - Why is it relaxing?
Here they come.
(Thankfully, more customers arrive.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
I'll help you with your order.
One beef burger?
(Bobbing his head)
- What did they order? - Nothing yet.
Kyung Soo has become one of us already.
The moment our eyes met, he asked, "What did they order?"
Pizza?
No, they haven't ordered yet.
We really look like people...
who work at a restaurant.
This is how they actually do it. They'll listen in,
and as soon as they say the menu, they'll go and start cooking.
(That's what she's doing.)
And...
like a minute after you're seated, the food is served.
Thank you.
(They finish placing their orders.)
Here comes the order. It's Table Three.
One pizza, one shrimp burger, one beef burger,
and one rice cracker taco.
(Silent)
Answer.
- Yes. - Yes.
(Nervous sigh)
He's so scary.
- I'm scared, Eun Ji. - That was scary.
- I'll make one of each ade. - He's the director.
- Is the director a bit... - He's the director.
You have to understand the director.
I sold a pizza by recommending it.
- Really? - Yes.
That was super nice.
Good job.
(Basking in the director's compliment)
He's really become part of the team.
I mean, he's the director.
(Annoyed)
(She focuses on cooking for now.)
(Young Ji starts making a burger.)
It's sizzling.
(Satisfied)
You use your core strength for it.
- Yes, that's right. - Right.
(Table 3: 1 rice cracker taco)
This is one serving.
We'll serve it with a shrimp burger and a beef burger.
Okay.
The timing was perfect, wasn't it?
- It was perfect. - It was perfect.
(She splashes water with ease...)
(and gives out a performance in steam.)
(Table 3: 1 beef burger combo, 1 shrimp burger combo)
- Great. - Let's go. Here's the beef burger.
Okay.
- We're on our way. - Let's go.
- Okay. - Here are some pickles. Enjoy.
Please give it a nice stir.
We're unbelievable, aren't we?
It feels good to serve them all at once, Eun Ji.
It does feel good when things are in sync.
- I'm comfortable. - Gosh. Today,
it's going so well.
Everything is running smoothly...
all thanks to Kyung Soo.
- Seriously. - That's right.
- Yes. - He can serve,
cook, and prep.
He can do it all.
Is there anything you can't do, Kyung Soo?
(Broken)
Things like this.
(Now, the pizza is finished too.)
- Which table? - Table Three.
- We'll serve Table 3. - Table 3 is all set.
(Table 3: Everything is served.)
It's going so smoothly.
It's my first time seeing Eun Ji sitting in the hall.
(Hello?)
What's going on?
I think tteokbokki was the source...
- of all disasters. - Right.
It's because it was ordered...
- by every table. - That's right.
You should make tteokbokki tomorrow, Young Ji.
- I know. Since it's the last day. - Yes.
(While the kitchen team vows to expand the menu items...)
Look in the mirror.
Watch this.
- It's the same, isn't it? - We do look alike.
Yes.
You're the same.
And this one looks like Young Ji.
Ex-boyfriend toast?
Eun Ji, what should we... They're coming.
(The customers they've been eagerly waiting for)
Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
Please come inside.
Nice to meet you, everyone.
- A party of three? - Yes.
How big is the pizza?
It's just the right size for three.
It's a ghost pepper pizza.
The ghost pepper is one...
- of the spiciest peppers. - Right.
Our pizza is just delicious.
It's deliciously spicy.
- Welcome. - It's about as spicy as Buldak.
While you're waiting,
- feel free to look at the posters. - It's good with the sauce.
- Welcome. - Thank you.
They're coming.
Bring it on.
(She puts her guard up right away.)
(She doesn't back down either.)
Slash through the air.
(Slashing)
Gosh. She's good.
(The next customers come in without giving them a break.)
Welcome.
Feel free to look around while you're waiting.
Gosh. They're coming. They're rushing in.
We'll have three orders rushing in soon.
Three orders will rush in consecutively.
- Okay. Thank you. - Thank you.
- There's a self-service station. - Okay.
- You can go upstairs now. - Thanks.
Thank you. Welcome.
I love you as much as the space.
Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
- Too much rice cake in a burger... - Shrimp.
Too much rice cake in a burger
Plump shrimp pop all over
She changed it again. She keeps changing the lyrics.
She keeps changing the words.
(No one can stop her.)
Also, one ghost pepper pizza.
Pardon?
One ghost pepper pizza.
- Pardon? - One ghost...
- Ghost pepper pizza. - You're good.
Ghost pepper pizza. You'll add that to your order.
And a cake.
The carrot cake Yu Jin likes.
Okay.
That will be 62.30 dollars.
And Lee Eun Ji's performance too.
Do you want it now?
- Now? - When you serve the food.
- Do you know about the price? - Yes.
Please pay for that afterward.
(The head chef was sending out the burgers.)
Here's one shrimp burger.
- We'll serve it with the beef one. - Okay.
(She spreads the sauce for the beef burger.)
(But she spread the sauce for the shrimp burger.)
How could I make such a mistake?
(She starts to let things slip.)
- Customers are coming. - Okay.
- Welcome. Hello. - What?
It's crazy.
I can't...
What is your name?
Come on. When customers are thrilled to see Kyung Soo,
I'm jealous.
I'll go out there. It won't be the same.
(Asking for their attention)
- Then we'll get... - Yes?
Do you need the receipt?
(Disappointed)
(Jealous again)
Like that.
- I'll call out the orders. - Okay.
- One shrimp. - Okay.
And 1 taco and 1 pizza.
- And one beef burger. - Okay.
Pomegranate ade and yuzu ade.
(She plans to win over the customers with ades.)
(She fills the glasses with ice.)
(Then she fills them up with sparkling water.)
- I'll serve this one. - Shrimp, pomegranate, and yuzu.
(While the refreshing ades are being prepared,)
(Mimi starts making a large batch of tacos.)
(She adds various spices.)
(It's time to set out 9 rice crackers.)
Please focus.
One, two, three, four,
five,
six, seven, eight,
and nine.
I counted like that before too.
- Hot stuff coming through, Eun Ji. - Okay.
(The pizza is cooked well.)
We just need a cake now.
- I'll get the cake ready. - Okay.
I just take this out and...
- And stick in the carrot. - And I stick the carrot in.
- And stick in the shovel. Done. - And the shovel.
That's right.
(He makes the desserts without a problem now.)
We're so on top of this that...
What are we going to do when we look so cool?
Listen, we're...
Will it be boring because we're so good at this?
In that case, someone should mess up the orders.
(Watch what you're saying all the time.)
- I'll take them to Table 7. - Yes, go to Table 7.
- Table 7. - Yes, Table 7.
- Here are your dishes. - Okay.
This is... Goodness.
- Are you all right? - My goodness.
I'll bring the cleaning cloth right away.
- Thank you. - Sorry.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
(Things were going a little too smoothly.)
- Thank you. - Here. Here are some tissues.
We're sorry. You must be busy.
No.
Why don't I take the ice cubes on this tray?
(She calms the customers down.)
It's hard to get rid of them.
(And she cleans up the mess in a calm manner.)
(Yu Jin comes back after cleaning the table.)
Did they finish it?
- They spilled it. - Did they spill it?
(The bad news reaches the kitchen.)
Should I make a new one for them?
- Was it pomegranate ade? - Yes. One pomegranate ade.
(Going at it without hesitation)
(Adding the ice cubes)
(And pouring the sparkling water)
(Hoping they won't spill it this time,)
Here it is.
(he makes it in no time.)
This is on the house.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Yes. Please enjoy.
(Feeling sorry)
She's as beautiful on the inside as she is on the outside.
(Biting)
Listen, Kyung Soo.
We need you tomorrow too.
That's right.
He's so good at this.
(He pretends he didn't hear it.)
(Hunting him again)
(Getting closer one step at a time)
(Startled)
Hello. Welcome.
- He was like a real waiter. - Welcome.
He was laughing like this, then he went,
"Hello. Welcome."
Yes. The menu is over here.
I think bulgogi pizza should be served last...
- if you consider it a meal. - Bulgogi?
- If you consider it a meal. - Bulgogi?
No, it's not bulgogi. What was the name of it?
- The ghost pepper pizza. - I got your point.
- That will be all. - Are you good?
Okay. I'll take your payment now.
(The bulgogi... No, the ghost pepper pizza is ready.)
- Good luck. - Let's do this.
- We have an order. - Okay.
- Who is this for? - Table Seven.
- That's Table Seven. - I'll take it.
- Bulgogi... Table Seven is all set. - Okay.
I love you, Table Seven.
Here's your...
ghost...
pepper pizza.
Here it is.
- Thank you. - Gosh. Thanks.
Are you going clubbing after this?
You are all glammed up.
- We dressed up for you. - Thank you.
I recommend taking a stroll in the Forest Park...
- in Yeonnam-dong. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Have a good time.
- Thank you. - Yes.
- As for tomorrow, - Yes.
we're going to work in total chaos.
- MOT. - So, today...
- What are you trying to say, MOT? - Today,
- Is it okay? - we can relax a bit.
You can choose your order here.
(At that moment, he's taking an order at the counter.)
We have an order, but there's a special request.
When you make the tacos,
stir-fry the beef separately and serve it separately...
like a vegetarian dish.
- Are they vegan? - Okay.
They also ordered the pizza.
- Yes. - You can leave out the ham only.
- Just the ham. Okay. - Cheese is fine.
I'm nervous. We have vegan customers.
- It's our first time. - Our first vegan customers.
In that case,
do I stir-fry the meat separately?
Everyone is nervous right now.
You can stir-fry the meat and serve it on a separate plate.
Okay.
Yes, this one. Don't add the chorizo.
Got it.
(She spreads the cheese evenly.)
Mushrooms.
(Then she adds the mushrooms only.)
(After putting it in the oven, it's ready.)
(Meanwhile, Mimi stir-fries the meat.)
Which plate should I serve this on?
(Yu Jin comes to help.)
- Is this big enough? - Yes.
(Worried)
Good. It's great.
Awesome.
(The taco with the beef on the side is ready.)
And we just need to finish up the pizza.
(Pizza without chorizo is ready too.)
Here's the pizza without ham.
(All dishes are served.)
(Next customers walk in.)
Welcome.
Take a look at the menu and let me know what you'd like.
- Is there coriander in the taco? - Yes?
We have a separate coriander pesto.
- Do you want us to leave it out? - Yes.
Okay. We'll leave it out.
A beef burger and a taco.
Okay.
One beef burger
- One rice cracker taco - Taco
(Setting up their stations according to the orders)
(She's gotten used to making the rice cracker tacos.)
(She's comfortable making the beef burger...)
(as it's her 3rd day making it.)
After serving this,
(The main dishes are ready in no time.)
I need to check.
Let's serve the tacos...
- with the beef burger, Mimi. - Okay.
They'll be ready soon.
I think I can really sell tacos.
You're selling them right now.
(Chuckling)
You're doing it right now.
(Operating as usual)
The taco is ready.
Okay. Wait for me.
Okay. I'll wait a little.
Let's serve them together
(The clingy head chef wants to serve them together.)
(She grills the patty with care.)
(Director Doh finds the unserved rice cracker taco.)
Wait for me.
The last customer asked for no pesto.
(Amazed)
I'm meticulous.
Okay. You can go ahead.
Will the beef burger be ready soon?
Not just soon. In 30 seconds.
One, two...
Uno, dos,
- Tres, cuatro. - tres, taco.
(Running away after getting steamed)
- Should I serve Table 11? - Yes, thank you.
Sir, take this one with you too.
- How long? - He needs to serve it separately...
because there's no room for it.
How long will you take?
Just 20 seconds.
- Then I can serve them together. - Is it possible?
Now, 20.
- Coming in 19, 18... - In 19, 18...
Seventeen.
Sixteen.
(Watching)
Fifteen.
Fourteen.
(She stacks up the burger while scattering the arugula.)
- Thirteen. - Make it pretty.
- Let's go. - Are you coming with me?
This way.
- Delivery for Table 11. - Young Ji.
(The customers cheer as the legendary chef appears.)
- Lee Young Ji. - Hello.
(Shy)
- Your yuzu ade. - I came to deliver it myself.
- Your pomegranate ade. - Thank you.
- Please enjoy your dinner. - Enjoy.
- Is everything all right? - Yes.
- We even ate the paper. - You shouldn't eat the paper.
- Was the food okay? - Yes. We loved it.
The burger was so good.
(I made it.)
I'm here to do market research.
- What did you like the most? - I loved them all.
- I liked the pizza the most. - The pizza.
- How was the burger? - It was so good.
The bun was so crispy.
It tasted very healthy. I loved the sauce too.
Everything is made with rice cake, including the pizza dough.
- It's a rice cake store. Enjoy. - It was so delicious.
- Did you enjoy your meal? - It was the best.
- Pardon? - It was delicious.
- The shovel... - Is there a problem?
- No, I just want one more shovel. - Additional shovel.
- I see. Of course. - Sorry.
Why is Young Ji taking so long?
It's making me nervous.
(As the head chef takes longer upstairs,)
(they feel nervous in the kitchen.)
Are you enjoying it?
- Yes. It's delicious. - I have a question.
- What is it? - What is this?
It's rice crackers.
Well, this is...
- You can say it in Korean. - It's rice cake.
- Rice cake. - And we fry it.
- It's deep-fried rice cake. - Got it.
I'll go downstairs and ask.
(The employee comes out to meet her as she's worried.)
Young Ji, is there something wrong?
Table Five wants another shovel.
- Another shovel? - And they asked me...
about the rice cracker.
But I had no idea.
- Ask Director Doh. - They wanted me to explain.
Director.
Director Doh, what are the rice crackers?
- They're rice cake puffs. - You puff up...
How can I explain it when they ask, "What is this?"
- "These are rice crackers." - The rice cake...
- Rice cake is... - I said we fried them.
The rice crackers are rice cakes made into puffs.
- I see. Like rice puffs. - Rice puffs.
How will you explain the rice puffs?
Rice puffs are rice puffs. Just go to Table Five.
Are they foreigners?
- Yes. - I see.
(Laughing)
- What should I say? - It's a Korean...
traditional snack.
- Rice snacks. - Rice is puffed.
- Rice is popped. - Puffed.
Rice went pop!
(She goes back without getting a good tip.)
Rice is popped.
Rice crackers are...
Korean rice cake popped!
Korean rice cake.
(Nodding for some reason)
- Did you say, "Rice goes pop!" - How did you explain it?
I said, "Rice cake, pop!"
(Good job.)
- Do we have six parties? - Yes.
(Space Rice Cake is currently packed.)
(Everyone is enjoying their dishes.)
- It feels strange, Yu Jin. - It does, doesn't it?
- Is it the calm before the storm? - It's even scarier, isn't it?
I'm sleepy.
I'm so sleepy all of a sudden.
- You're sleepy, right? - Yes. All of a sudden.
- Do you know why you're sleepy? - Why?
Because we're not busy.
Why aren't we busy?
You're sleepy because we're not busy.
(Keeping the place clean when they're not busy)
(And it's selfie time.)
(Approaching)
- Yu Jin. What are you doing... - Yes?
- when we're working? - I was just...
- I was enjoying my free time. - Okay.
Come on.
(Embarrassed)
(When everyone is enjoying the downtime,)
(a customer cautiously approaches the counter.)
As for the burger,
the patty isn't cooked.
- The patty isn't cooked? - No.
- I see. - It's undercooked in the middle.
- I'll go check. - Sure.
- What's your table number? - Table 11.
- Okay. Table 11. - Young Ji.
- Yes? - Young Ji.
A customer said the patty wasn't cooked inside.
- Where is this? - Go upstairs and check Table 11.
(There's a complaint about the patty.)
(She rushes to the 2nd floor.)
Thank you.
Let's get ready, Eun Ji. What should we do?
A song won't cut it for an undercooked patty.
We need to go and give a full 90-degree bow.
- We bow and take it off the bill. - We can't joke about this.
(Young Ji reaches the hall in the meantime.)
My goodness.
Is it supposed to be this red?
Would you be okay if I made a new one for you?
(Coming up next)
(We had such fun.)
(The last day of Space Rice Cake)
(What's the revived dish on the last day of business?)
(The long-missed flavors of Goheun are back!)
(This is my identity.)
(It's really good.)
(That's me.)
(They dream of a happy ending.)
(I did the math, and you're in the red.)
(A devastating piece of news comes out of nowhere.)
(We want more customers to come!)
(Their final sprint to climb out of the red)
(They take walk-ins on the fly.)
(We sell tteokbokki!)
(While they started out ambitiously,)
(due to a torrential downpour,)
(the streets are empty with no customers.)
(Please come in.)
(Dizzy)
(It's deja vu from their first day of business.)
(An incredible bookend)
(Will they be unable to turn a profit?)
(The final sales report)
(The result of 10 long days of business)
(A heated dispute erupts over the unbelievable results.)
(I'll bring my notebook.)
(From interrogations sparked by suspicion...)
(to fierce backlash against the HQ's decision)
(Where did all the hard work of the past 10 days go?)
(Space Rice Cake is on the brink of running at a loss.)
(Will they turn things around?)